Let's meditate, shout, Islam, you're
our iPhone,
relax your mouth,
relax your eyes, 7,
pull in your stomach, a little tired, channel, and
put your fingers marked, butt, everything,
soft forehead, forza,
remember the slight smile, name, medal, smiley,
kidsmart,
Yana, let
's start, then the children seemed quickly, Dan
Balan, and about the air, exhale, at the end of this,
you're a good girl,
now abrasive molex, thermal, and now
pay attention to the wedding, earlier in the morning,
even mount, calm, peaceful,
baseball cap, another one above, free from the
bustle of the day,
now look back, this week,
in everything, we're returning to our normal life.
Xenical, we worked, think about the
work we must face
when we get home.
Me, be the last to know,
ride, sleep, lift,
and about those people who
start to give you problems or difficulties at
home. Steve Vai, but this week we
look without you back, redemption,
pull out, yes, well, besides this peace, and we
cannot deny
the difficulties that ours is on that
next week, when you come to my
Hindu, you're a kunik
two and look  send as speed
increases your breathing and heartbeat increases
yubiki hearts and how you will
lose the state that was
here diamond length passed when you
face problems at work with
problems in the family
state of mind here is a retreat and us
contrast this is the next day this
happens after every retreat all over the
world we want to find out
the state of this mind
retreat she remained us as soon as
we approach the airport we are already
beginning to lose this state of mind and the mind
becomes the best baguette busy
tense problems at home problems at
work again blindly
rise in front of you labor the wind begins to
disturb the calm state of the water
this week we studied negative
emotions
about the state of nervousness that you get
upset when you meet people with a
negative attitude it is also like a nose
that cannot exist without getting angry
we should become attached to the face
this nervousness seems to be the previous
next week and the desire to avoid
people difficult situations
and they are all like but themselves based
on the face on the misunderstanding where
things actually come from because we do not
know what to do he orders him but
this misunderstanding
try
to choose one person or a difficult
The situation that will be next
week and think about the pen,
think 20 what seeds I planted
so that this person would be my life,
was this situation my life, have you done
something similar with other people, this is planting
seeds
and us, and more precisely, these seeds will
open, the address flew out among,
check what small things you
do, the
second rule of karma is a small family, but a
complex person grows up, not a difficult situation, I
should do something similar, he
is brought up, but something much smaller, the
second rule of food is not enough,
so try to guess what you are doing
yourself
to create this husband who yells
at you, which comes out of you in pieces,
now think about the good seeds
that you can plant even on the way
home,
they do that can fix these garden
situations in general, we have a choice
to make pins singers
accept our mistakes that we made
in relation to others, a week to study 7
that you can correct, which we
can deploy
AvtoVAZ, this is
paraffin islands, but it seems to me many of
us on the react, we would better respond to
positive 7 back 20 let's first
figure it out 20 a complex person, not a
difficult situation, let's submitted from a
positive seeds which can
Sow, think about a person, for example,
who causes you dependency. We can't
focus on being happy
for the quality of votes. This person
is happier. The best way
to fix this is to make a small
plan for next week. How to sow
good, fresh, happy families that are
antidotes to the problems that await you.
Three lengths can wait for you now. Exhale, don't open your
eyes. Send karma to the Sindacco for the
difficult work of students.
Send it to the
whole world as a gift. The price is on your
exhale. The language of very intelligent, living, doom, 3 by
2 color shares.
Now open your eyes. Do some
stretching. Tanks. 0.
Any questions or comments? Ideas. MicroSD.
Things that can be invented that can help
other people.
Thank you for this wonderful meditation. I
had a small website.  Plain sight running gear,
nothing and nothing with its own
nature, Mazda
empty network, I invited him to visit, he passed, everyone is
watching, these are oranges of the Leo sign, your Persian, general,
where are the seeds that I think the game is,
his gun, in fact, I see them as
good, all the seeds, they’re just not her, the
handle which I think is true, good
omens are people who are faces under
which pain was caused, very often we can
indicate that time has passed and a breakthrough is on us, a
bunch of stripes at work, we had
health problems and we have
seeds so that all this is seen, the problem is
if our seeds improve,
history is rewritten, this is called
historical, to revise
historical events, the source and you
begin to
revise these stories, they become
kill, this is not you see this, that’s
not this match, the stove, the girl made her
fingers, it doesn’t hurt, or is this and in this there is
I was fired, this is actually
Buddha gave me the opportunity,
let’s survive,
find a better partner, the best job, I
applied life, I will apply time,
after which I completed a degree in
studying which study stones, I
applied these, I knew I remembered that I was looking for a
job, I went to one interview, an iPhone, and
the owner of the jewelry store, a lawyer, and
he  He didn't make me wait because my
mom came.
I saw that a man came in and took it
because   He
came in, he found a gun pointed at his
head, and the girl stood smiling, and her
mother looked, I hope, and said, I'm not worried,
everything will be fine, the man
shot, and the girl realized this and started
screaming,
I'm collecting, and we rhyme, I can't make
payments,
then I met my future
business partner, we
built a large sales company ourselves,
bow to those bad seeds
when you, three, you were refused thirty times
in other stores,
maybe somewhere there were actually good
seeds, not bad, yes, therefore, 7 must
actually not empty, like Irochka, sacred, and as
you live, they can
change, and this is a large part of tantra,
thank you for the students, I want to share 7,
what happened to me during 50 when
I was little, I looked at the sky and
I had a desire
to stop all wars, that people are angry,
and after
12 years,
the author of methane realized that it is impossible, yes, I
got older, the tail, and began to think that
everything exists with itself and I ca
n’t change it. Yesterday, during
hydration, I connected with myself at
three or four years old,
and I realized that this is possible, thank you for
this feeling, remove it now I   connected with
myself the
brush I feel whole also I
saw your book in the sixteenth
year in April when you had a meeting with
Mr. on guardianship on ios you were disrupted by
Mr. Norbekov the
content of these nasty winter fears of gays and and
he gave you as yesterday all the rivers said
what she is I am MS I am a Muslim there is a dream to
unite all religions may not be a
lexeme of people about free video editing because
some of our people are in Kazakhstan
and the peasants are orthodox  policy people
at
I want to unite everyone unity them u
can connect all over the
world Yuma Benson thank you for the
teaching and please 1
let me tell you this miracle also
came to me because today is Easter there are
two big
holidays when Christina Christmas and
Easter thin marriage and so me and my family we
went what is the purpose for during Easter I
remember when I first went to church I still
go I remember my mother brought me there she
said get on your knees and I said
why because  you'll never kneel in your life
and so they hold their
hands in front of them, sort of an hour's feat,
okay, mom, what should I do? Pray for
everyone. What does it mean to
pray?
She said, think about someone you love
from Odessa and send them good
thoughts. I wish you a whole life on the road. Okay,
mom, that's mom, you should do it for everyone.
I remember I closed my eyes on
Easter and passed by, and then I want you to be
happy and healthy and everything is fine. Then I
thought, mopar.by, I hope that those are
good. Then I thought, and then someone is
tugging at me. We need to get through.
I haven't finished yet.
You said to think about everything. I just
approached dialectics. Yes, I understand, but you
really can't pray for everyone.
It's really impossible. I have to try.
I'll finish, just thinking. There are still
seven and a half billion left.
I understand, but we need to get through. They're closing
our church. Perhaps this is also the leader with
oars. It's impossible. Stop the war.
It's impossible. And she's somewhere around 16
years old. You understand that it's impossible.
Prayer doesn't work. And yet, cartoons,
which,
and somehow, in her mind.  Give up and cameras and
would find something impossible to think that it is
impossible to found you during the
Vietnam War, I already wanted to
stop the war later I thought that this is
January this is impossible
and during the time we say let's
become a virus, so solve your
problems for the next salt balance by
planting good families there are those who
treat me badly instead of
talking to them fight
I will just try to change my
seeds Odessa and first of all they will
change secondly I will become happy happy
every day to everyone and
they began to notice that you have become different
and then maybe they will ask you to teach
them leaves and course 1 I will become a virus I
became a farce father he teaches horse wives who does
not teach Peter and Masha Masha and the guy
goes and does not teach hundreds of people I can not
travel all over the world and pray I will show
but I can be a virus I can start
tracking I can start this explosion I can
be the very first.  I can't be the
beginning of this virus.
If John is successful, then Ikon will be
successful. If they are successful, then Peter and
Masha will be successful. If they study and students
want to learn how to be
happy, this will be a plus. It doesn't come naturally.
DNS, come up with this method.
I recently thought about ceremonies in a puzzle.
You can change the whole world. You can
pray for a very long time. You can influence
each person. This is 100 people.
Successful
inside, successful
outside, successful copy you.
This way, you pray
for all people. You, with your skirt,
my mother was right and at the same time,
wrong. My mother herself does other things. The hall is
torn down. There will be a line. He was running around for
5-4-4. Gamma says cleverly, they should
plant so that the shores are clear.
I can't understand the connection between that family
year, the name of which he
spoke about, as if it is not
revealed. Sometimes, Tim Tim, I want to add
this story with Mom,
class seven or eight, which is where we
say both numbers. The dwarf added this
story about Mom,
who somehow, this is technically a question for what
I did to someone, then I do
four forces.
Pars, what does it say in the morning,
diamond, limit data if I
did something to someone, I'm talking about sub-1 rank. In fact,
a car accident should happen, but according to the sutra, my heart will
just hurt my head. And if I
do four, but if you
and if we do this, what happens is
global peace and justice about
sales tax and I am my child, we teach, we submit
4, whether if so, then
how can we leave
your bad seeds. The
app is that dorozh as soon as you teach
one can bead others how to do the 4
forces business very carefully search in a suit, this
means I understand,
especially means one handle, this is true
xn with his old seeds helped,
this is this level, this is very must be in
your group
where you relay races will look for this for
access to these people,
PR played, they already have a
lifelong plan, they decided not to do not plant
such seeds, but they will open
everything here, that's why we
teach intrigue to children by whom p.g.
Gameplay
door
and at first, we teach on Twitter. Yes,
you can. For the fact that HQ I eat about
flowering plants.
Yes, this is very reasonable. But if you go to the
Maldives, if you do this again, then the
second level,
the law of karma, level. We start talking
about planting a
watermelon here. Politics will open. This is also
how to put a name on
wet paper. It starts to bloom three days
ago,
painfully. They won't open at all. This is how they were
killed. You force them to open prematurely and their Atterson. You thereby approve of them so that they come out, but they are too small to understand. The question is not so. Allah, which creation, which relates to them, barberry, I do this. This means if I killed someone, what should mint do? It shouldn't
end with simple special
seeds, good
masses, but also watch your nose. Now it
will fall and I want to stay with me.
Casio pirates of Dvina, Stens. How are you doing?
How are you doing? I'm running to
you for a quick sleep to Themis. That's why I want to
speed them up. I drop a place for what.
Just be happy.
About what you're doing, speeding up the topic. 7
likes the old one, and the piece of how you
then speed up so that bad contacts are cool.
I have a simple answer regarding the iris above, that the
bad ones sprouted very quickly, my
recommendations
went in and became large. Is this a
misunderstanding? Your misunderstanding is forcing the
seeds to grow quickly and to large sizes.
Therefore, the level of 4 forces is not just
a promise not to do that, the length of the route
4 forces itself shows. You
understand the sizov chance of the reasons why
mandus 4 forces work whole. If you
do this and understand this beginning, you
understand what seeds are.
This is not just a promise not to fly. Hamas is the
wrong karmic. Sen. 2
hamster with cinder bala town say business
choker banana village understanding for the family
dies who were imprisoned when a
person was killed key or dies if you do
business four villages in Spain beaten to 40 by
Kim with understanding Kim am-am fingers,
it mixes with him since oils
if you walk along but
destroys it. The fourth law of karma,
which says that if we do something,
she in childhood  We'll be back, guys, have you
seen my watch? Omax, thank you. You
always ask a difficult question. Maybe here's an
easy question.
Legally, not the way. They took him to the forest. An
easy question. Who killed one? We're not sitting here. A
question I still don't understand and would
forgive. Externally, I found the answer to
your teachings.
Consciousness, trust in everything. There's a
reason. There's no one. There's no one. There's an
example.
Yes, that's what I'm starting. What was the beginning. With a
knife, and the platform. I'm 2020.
This model is an action. Study. They call. I don't
understand. Here are
scientists and anarchists. The mystery is when it
became specific. What does he not understand?
Because I'm learning with difficulties. It ended.
Steaming. Dear, yes, when
I started life the day before, he addressed them in no way. They weren't
idiots and kicked them and there was no prize. He did
n't like them. He thinks it
was very unpleasant. You agree. They live
and the cycle to the city is very poor.
Two cars, a broken apartment,
not very good. While the evil spirits are copper, he never even
brushes his teeth. They were in no hurry. How do you
live there? And I don't know. This man is always
shouting at us, too. He's shouting at us. Disk, and that's where the
world comes from. Let's
say he drew it online. Thank you for
asking.
I'll find out about him, get him,
never spoil the skinny barrel, that he's
always right, Julia, maybe the sky isn't
blue, and he'll prove it, and at the end of the disc you'll
fail, then it's better to shut up and go
clean it. Science is developing
incorrectly, incorrectly, and here's the basis of Squix's cuts,
and again to the wrong hole, and I
think that the basis is in the mind, but it's not a
salon day, everything has a reason,
I'm sitting there, and because America is
inventing everything, you also study them at
school in America, that in China, for a moment, they came up with
supports, in China, they came up with
500 years of farrah than in America, on my nose,
but at school or somewhere big, that in
America it was invented, this is what we came up with, it will turn out
he's like, yes, that's the main thing, in
principle, they say that the basis of science is the
reasons, the reasons, that's how Jayda is, cool, I did
n't think that this scam is not a
trap,
according to science, everything has a reason, you
have a question, now tell me, please,
how the star of everything should be a game, and first,
therefore, there should be a first
reason for good, it was the first
reason
with which it all began.  Everything has a
reason, a farce of the hidden, there must be
some beginning, and by the way, this is the most
important thing, there must be a beginning, could you please
tell me what is the
first thing, thank you for asking,
Arsen, there was a big explosion, like a warehouse, and everything was there, everyone
was compressed, a wacom, a laundress
the size of a dream, a lot of energy was here,
his day, it exploded, and this is the super
root cause of everything, all the planets and stars,
people, everything, this is the first moment, the first
reason, thank you for explaining science to me,
and you tell me what was the reason for
this reason, and I'm leaving that, I think
you're telling us now that there is something to be tired of
before the explosion, the explosion,
I attach it, but that didn't have a reason, the
foundation, the sounds that everything has,
spent, then they gave a yurt of languages, besides
everything, well,
there, go away, get out of my room, don't
say who came to you, it's just 1 to 8, there
can't be first reasons for this,
I'm according to Blair's laws, on TV, pi don
calo, especially according to science, the
index, if you find them, you spend
five minutes with you, moreover, if you spend my, no, it
easily freezes for you, that can't be the
first reason, this  Impossible, yes, if there
is a first reason for everything, without a tone
that doesn't have one, and after three cheers,
this is for when all the sciences aren't given, dance,
if you want these spaghetti mats
like noodles with baby-g that have no
end, help reasons, a black picture,
just a drive, sucka, begins, completo,
spaghetti 2, continues, the
past interview stretches into the future,
endlessly, and there are three four things, a
project to chat, this is spaghetti, no, they didn't
start, no, the beginning of growth, for a reason, a
reason is needed, a movie, in
Buddhism, everything, and in Buddhism, everything that
changes, they still have a beginning, a
result, when you want a child, it
was in it, saddened, children, this is also the
reason for us, I'll post it on the last day, and for
five years, the beginning, you know,
everything is chosen from the package, first, it
means playing, that you took something from them,
shamans, nothing produces anything, it couldn't
happen, something somewhere,
when I was little, childhood,
I must have done something, good, this is the best
song of my childhood, and now, and now
it goes into the future, so we convinced ourselves,
in our hope, it begins, if there is no reason to
look, or the future is endless,
let's call it a run, life from died,
happens first  experience and noted and noted.
This spaghetti received after this point, you are
no longer a virgin
or a virgin after you, but many people, like this,
of us, micro spaghetti, they
know this day, the
levers of the Ketu line, it was before, and then
another person before this, in virgins
after Man Mo, the camera of Lima, a lawyer for
all living beings, I, in the first perception,
eliminate this as a sign on this
spaghetti, man on me,
and from this point, whether you or not, and people
who have not seen the emptiness inside the post,
you will
never be left without online online
more than 3 means that I noted
you do not suffer, you no longer suffer
youtube red flame a person who
suffers all the time, come on to this point and
after that, not mine either, never
happens from a blow, there is pain, and this is that
sign, here and all yours, whether the body
changes, it becomes a
diamond, the body of a diamond, all your
lives change,
think, I sum up, find, remember the
conversation, in short, when you think that there is a
beginning